

NOÈ VILLANUEVA MOYA

APP DEVELOPER (C#, KOTLIN, SWIFT)

Ø

(+34) 620 73 59 37

Sant Pere de Ribes

 \boxtimes

nvillanuevamoya@gmail.com



<u>GitHub</u>

ABOUT ME

I am a young Developer graduated in **DAMv**, supplementing with additional training in a **Bootcamp** in **Mobile Application Development**.

I consider myself a person who has always liked to **explore** and **investigate** everything around her, and it is thanks to this that programming **motivated** me from day one. My goal is to **keep growing** and improving to contribute to **innovative** and **ambitious projects**. I'm willing to take on new challenges and I have a lot of desire to add **value to the sector**.

So far I have worked with **C#**, **Kotlin** and **Swift** and I have developed several **personal** and **academic** projects. One of the most outstanding projects I've done is *ITB Infected*, where I developed a horror video game set in an institute.

EDUCATION

BOOTCAMP IN MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

ANDROID & iOS | 430h

EURECAT ACADEMY, BARCELONA MAR 2024 - IUL 2024

HNC IN MULTI-PLATFORM APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT, DIGITAL ENTERTAIMENT AND VIDEOGAMES (DAMV)

INSTITUT TECNOLÒGIC DE BARCELONA 2021-2023

UNIVERSITY DEGREE IN APPLIED STATISTICS

(Not finished)

UNIVERSITAT AUTÒNOMA DE BARCELONA 2020-2021

INTEREST DATA

- Driving license permit B.
- Availability of own vehicle.
- Athlete and amateur soccer player.

FrontEnd

JSON HTML CSS JavaScript TypeScript XML Figma

PROJECTS

BackEnd

SKILLS

C# Kotlin Swift

Database

MySQL PostgreSQL MongoDB

Frameworks

Unity Odoo .NET

Tools

GitHub Android Studio Xcode Visual Studio

WORK EXPERIENCE

BUSINESS APPLICATION ENGINEER JUNIOR

DXC TECHNOLOGY, BARCELONA | FEB 2023 - JUN 2023

Internship in the tSocial project within the program of Digital Transformation of the Social Benefits processing (Generalitat de Catalunya):

- Use of databases, SQL queries, JSON documents and JIRA management.
- Resolution of JIRA tickets related to social benefits claimants.

BAR WAITER

PENYA BARCELONISTA AITANA BONMATÍ | JUN - SET 2023 / 2024 LA XIXONENCA | JUN -SET 2019 / 2020 / 2021

Customer service, food and beverage handling, sales control and table service. Organization and control of the establishment.

ROOM STEWARD

SERVIHOSTEL ETT S.L. | JUN 2022 - SET 2022

Preparation of the event space, reception of guests, food and beverage service.

LANGUAGES







SPANISH - native



GERMAN - A1.2 level (Goethe-Zertifikat A1)